quizup.com 2015-04-27

# QuizUp

## Plain Vanilla Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: 7 November 2013**

Your privacy is important to Plain Vanilla. This Privacy Policy covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store information that we receive when you use our Services (as defined in our Terms of Service, accessible at “Terms of use”). Please take a moment and read over our privacy policy and let us know if you have any questions. This Privacy Policy applies only to those websites, services and applications included within “Services” and doesn’t apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service.

### Collection and Use of PII

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services.

Here are some examples of the types of PII we may collect and how we may use it.

#### How we collect and use information

  * When you register we may collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information ( **“Personally Identifiable Information”** or **“PII”** ). 
  * We may use cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Services. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept cookies, you will not be able to stay automatically logged in to the Services.

#### How we use your PII

  * The PII we collect allows us to keep you posted on Plain Vanilla‘s latest Services and updates. Plain Vanilla and its affiliates may share PII with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our Services.
  * We also use PII to help us develop, deliver, and improve our Services.
  * From time to time, we may use your PII to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by unregistering at [unsubscribe@plainvanillagames.com](mailto:unsubscribe@plainvanillagames.com)
  * We may also use PII for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve Plain Vanilla’s Services and customer communications.

#### Collection and Use of Non-PII

We also collect non-PII − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-PII for any purpose. We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code, unique device identifier, location, and the time zone where the Services are used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our Services.

If we do combine non-PII with PII the combined information will be treated as PII for as long as it remains combined.

#### Disclosure to Third Parties

At times Plain Vanilla may make certain PII available to strategic partners that work with Plain Vanilla to provide products and services, or that help Plain Vanilla market to customers. For example, when you make a purchase through the Apps, you authorize Plain Vanilla and its third party payment processor to exchange the payment information you provide to us to carry out your purchase on the Services. PII will only be shared by Plain Vanilla to provide or improve our Services; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes. 

##### Service Providers

Plain Vanilla shares PII with companies who provide services such as hosting, information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys.. 

##### Others

It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental authorities within or outside your country of residence − for Plain Vanilla to disclose your PII. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or appropriate.

We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all PII we collect to the relevant third party.

#### Protection of PII

Plain Vanilla takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard your PII against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

When you use Plain Vanilla Apps or post on a chat room, or social networking service, the PII you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the PII you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a forum posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features. 

#### Integrity and Retention of PII

We will retain your PII for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

#### Access to PII

For other PII, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to such PII so you can request that we correct or delete the PII we have about you. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by contacting Plain Vanilla at [privacy@plainvanillagames.com](mailto:privacy@plainvanillagames.com).

#### Children

We do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the PII of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. 

#### Location-Based Services

In some cases we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you.

#### International Users

Information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. Your use of the Services followed by your submission of any PII represents your agreement to that transfer.

#### Our Companywide Commitment to Your Privacy

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

Plain Vanilla may update its Privacy Policy from time to time. Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. When we change the policy in a material way, we’ll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll indicate when such changes will become effective. a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.
